myregistrywedding.com 2018-06-11

# Privacy Policy | MYREGISTRYWEDDING

Myregistrywedding (“MRW”) is a platform for couples to publish their Registry Wedding and archive it for the future.Protecting the privacy and security of consumers’ information is very important to us. Our website serves the following functions:

provides couples with a platform to publish their registry wedding, Archive the pictures for future reference.This Privacy Policy describes the collection and use of information on our website and blog. Please read this policy before using, or submitting information to, these sites. By using this site, you signify that you agree to this Privacy Policy. Although this site contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other, sites. If you have questions about how those websites collect and use data, you should carefully read those sites’ privacy policies.

Personal Information Collected on this Website

No personal information is collected on this website from readers and couples who browse for information about  marriage, check registry wedding pictures or online advertising or who use the opt-out page.

The only personal information collected on this website is gathered on our “contact us” and Subscribe forms. In the subscribe form, fields are provided so that users can submit questions or comments and provide contact information such as email address, and phone number.  We collect this personal information so that we can respond to these inquiries, comments, and questions. We may share information submitted by consumers with member companies or other third parties to help resolve users’ complaints. We also may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, including by search warrant, subpoena, or court order. You do not need to disclose any personal information to MRW in order to submit a comment or complaint about MRW .However, we may be unable to respond or take appropriate action if your information is incomplete.

As discussed below, we also collect non-personally identifiable information on this website. However, we do not merge any of the personal information collected via our contact form with anonymous data collected on our website.

Non-Personally Identifiable Data Collected on this Website

We collect and store in server logs non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, IP address, operating system, the date and time of visits, the pages visited on the site, time spent viewing the site, and return visits to the site. We also use Google Analytics, a service that records non-personally identifiable data such as browser type, operating system, the date and time of a visit, where visitors came from, the pages visited on this website, the time spent viewing site, where visitors went when they left the site, and return visits to the site.

We aggregate this non-personally identifiable data to better understand how visitors use our site, and to help manage, maintain, and report on use of our website. We store IP addresses for fraud detection and prevention purposes.

We may share this non-personally identifiable data with third parties for the limited purpose of reporting on use of our website, or to comply with applicable law. We also may share this data with our service providers. We do not rent, sell or share any non-personally identifiable data collected on this website with third parties for marketing purposes.

Cookies

We use cookies on this website. Cookies are small text files created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of online patterns and preferences, as well as to identify return visitors. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information each time you visit a website.

We also serve cookies to help us anonymously track web traffic, as described above.

Please note that if you delete any opt-out cookies obtained using the MRW opt-out page, such as by clearing all cookies in your browser, you will need to return to the opt-out page to renew your choices.

You have the ability to manage the use of cookies on your computer using controls in your browser. To learn more about how to manage cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.

Third Party Content, Links, and Plug-ins

This site contains links to other websites not owned by MRW .Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other, sites. If you have questions about how those websites collect and use data, you should carefully read those sites’ privacy policies.

This site may also offer you the ability to interact with social plugins from social media sites, such as Facebook (facebook.com), Linkedin (linkedin.com) and Twitter (twitter.com). The social media sites may receive data when you visit a website — such as networkadverising.org — that has plugins. In some cases, MRW  may know that you clicked on a social plugin such as a Facebook Like button, or receive other information from the social media sites. Similarly, if you have previously provided personally identifiable information to a third-party operating a plug-in on this website, then this third-party may recognize you on this website. Your use of social network plugins is subject to each social media site’s privacy policy, which may be different from ours, so please read these policies carefully to understand their policies and your options. As with linked sites, MRW has no control over the information that is collected, stored, or used by social network plugins.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As our organization, membership, and services evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to reflect those changes. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect.

Questions?  
Please contact us with any questions about this website Privacy Policy by sending a mail to myregistrywedding@myregistrywedding.com
